Today we are going to start printing in the dark room.
One of the first things that you need to know how to do when you begin printing in your dark room is how to make your paper developer.
You hear I stress paper because there is a difference between paper developer and film developer and I know the first few times when I was in the dark room I didn't understand that.
It wasn't a really good experience doing it that way.
This is Kodak dectal paper developer.
I kind of like the way Kodak does it because it says right on the packaging "paper".
So this way, when you have film developer like I showed you on the last episode it says "film".
One important aspect about making this is that you have to understand it is a powder.
There are some film developers that are liquid.
When you begin making this again, it is a lot like making this, it is a lot like making a cake again.
It says right here what the temperature is you need to get.
It is very important, it is 90 to 100 degrees Fahrenheit.
It is very important that you get that water up to that temperature before you begin mixing it.